瞧  有人把狗带进餐厅呢
Look at that. Dogs in the diner.
以为我们这是哪啊  巴黎吗
Where are we, Paris?
如果这里真是巴黎  那老子要不喷除臭剂了
'Cause if we are, I'm gonna stop wearing deodorant.
你们看到那条可爱的狗了吗
Did you guys see that adorable dog?
别人在吃饭  它在旁边把狂犬病毒
You mean the one leaking rabies all over the table
滴得满桌子都是的那条狗吗
while people are trying to eat?
她说她的狗有准证啊
She said he's allowed to be in here.
是她已注册的情感伴侣
He's her registered emotional companion.
是她已注册的什么狗屁来着
Her registered full-of-crap what?
人家穿着正规的背心  上面写着
He's got one of those official vests that says
"请勿抚摸  我在工作"
"Don't pet me, I'm working."
我也有件衣服写着"联邦比基尼调查员"
I have a shirt that says "Federal Bikini Inspector,"
但不见美国政府真有这个部门啊
but there is simply no such branch of the U.S. government.
您好  这是什么玩意
Hi, so, uh, what the hell is this?
抱歉  你什么意思
Excuse me? I don't understand.
餐厅不允许带宠物入内
Dogs aren't allowed in the diner.
带他进来是符合法规的
Oh, he's legally allowed to be here.
他是我的已注册情感伴侣
He's my registered emotional companion.
意思就是你没男朋友
You mean you don't have a boyfriend.
不是  我有焦虑症
No, I suffer from anxiety.
意思就是你不想单独吃饭
You mean you don't want to eat alone.
不是  我有医生证明
No, I have a note from a doctor.
意思就是你家有网跟打印机
You mean you have a printer and the Internet.
老实承认  我就让狗待在这里
Admit it, and the dog can stay.
这年头男人太难找了
It's really hard meeting guys.
这才乖嘛  我去拿饼干给你吃
There's a good boy. I'll get you a cookie.
是我自己的错觉  还是阿憨说韩文时
Is it just me, or does Han sound kind of sexy
有着别样的性感啊
when he speaks Korean?
阿憨的身子  贝利·怀特的声音
Looks like Han, sounds like Barry White.
跟谁说电话呢  阿憨
Who was that, Han?
新交的性感韩国女朋友吗
Do you have a hot, new Korean girlfriend?
是啊  一个在电话上很爱你
Yeah, someone who really likes you
首分钟收费1块5
and is $1.50 for the first minute
之后每分钟2块的女人吗
and $2 for each additional minute?
我是在跟我妈说电话啦
I was talking to my mother!
所以我说的没错喽
So... yes?
刚不是在调情  是在道歉
I was not talking hot. I was apologizing.
她还在气我离家出国
She's still angry I left home.
她觉得我现在是游手好闲的美国人  不但嗑药
She thinks I'm freewheeling American who takes drugs
还跟卡戴珊般的拜金浪女乱搞
and has intercourse with dirty Kardashian.
她知道你都是去客制小熊店买毛衣的吗
Does she know you buy your sweaters at build-a-bear?
我是不太了解韩国文化啦
Well, I don't know a lot about the Korean culture,
不过你应该为自己抗争
but maybe you should stand up for yourself
别再只是一味地跟你妈道歉啊
and stop apologizing to your mother.
对啊  你有什么好道歉的啊
Yeah, what do you even have to apologize for?
你妈生你时  应该是全世界最轻松的了
You must have been the easiest birth ever.
她一咳嗽  就能把你喷进棒球手套里
She could've coughed you into a catcher's mitt.
我要弄杯卡布奇诺  你要喝吗
I'm making a cappuccino, you want one?
不行  我体内不能有咖啡因
Nope, I can't have any caffeine.
我明天要去当药物试验自愿者
I have to keep my system clean.
不能乱吃
I'm doing a drug trial tomorrow.
麦克斯  可别是在药物推出市场前
Max, not one of those places where they use you as a guinea pig
帮人实验有何副作用的人体小白鼠吧
to test for side effects of new drugs that go on the market?
依我看来更像是轻松赚五百
Or, as I like to call it, getting paid $500
副作用则凭运气
to, uh, roll the side effects dice
"产生幻觉"等于中头奖
and hope it lands on hallucinations.
打死我也不干这种事
I would never do something like that.
我待我身如圣堂
I consider my body a temple.
我前两晚貌似看到某人往"圣堂"里
Didn't I see your "temple" eat a bag
供奉了不少特辣膨化食品啊
of flaming hot cheetos two nights ago?
那人后悔至今
And that was a huge mistake.
我到现在还有点...
I still have a little...
"菊"辣如麻
Burny heinie.
而且  想想我造福了无数病友
And besides, think of all the people who are
让他们安全地降低胆固醇
lowering their cholesterol safely because of me.
还有救了那些差点就吃"柯拉米插"的人一命
Or the people who aren't taking Klamitra because of me.
我没听过"柯拉米插"这种药呢
I never heard of Klamitra.
大恩不言谢
You're welcome.
我认识"柯拉米插"
I know Klamitra.
是我健身房的性感黑妞教练
Sexy black woman who teaches my spin class.
您好  我想跟您问个人
Uh, hello, uh, maybe you can help me.
我要找卡洛琳·钱宁
I'm looking for Caroline Channing.
我有些法律问题要跟她谈谈
I have a legal matter to discuss with her.
谁啊  没见过  没听过
Never heard of her. Never seen her.
-哈钦森先生  -我没宣誓过要说实话
- Mr. Hutchinson? - Never took an oath.
天啊  哈钦森先生  好久不见
Oh, my God, Mr. Hutchinson, hi.
上次见你还是我爸的丑闻败露时
I haven't seen you since my father's scandal broke
你被人架出办公室那会儿呢
and they were dragging you out of your law offices.
我能抱你一下吗
Can I hug you?
事发后
I mean, it's been so long
我好久没见到当年的亲朋好友了
since I've seen anyone from my old life.
行  不过别抱太紧
But, uh, not too hard.
事发后  我得了胃酸倒流
Ever since the scandal, I've had acid reflux.
你以前好像比较高啊
Didn't you used to be taller?
身高没变  志气全无罢了
No, uh, prouder.
哈钦森先生  她是我朋友  麦克斯
Oh, uh, Mr. Hutchinson, this is my friend, Max.
麦克斯  他是里欧·哈钦森
Max, this is Leo Hutchinson,
我父亲的代表律师之一
one of my father's attorneys.
我还没真正见过...
Oh, I've never known a lawyer
非法院指派给我的律师呢
who wasn't court-appointed for me.
电视剧《法律与秩序》里的律师不算
Well, except for the ones on Law & Order.
你去演过那个剧吗
Have you ever been on that show?
没有  我是真正的律师
No, I'm a real lawyer.
可是你看着挺像剧中的演员
You look like someone who was on that show.
你真的没在食子母亲那集当辩护律师吗
Are you sure you didn't represent the woman who ate her child?
我从没在剧里为吃小孩的人辩护过
I've never represented anyone who ate their child.
不过现实生活就...
On Law & Order.
卡洛琳
Caroline,
抱歉把你牵扯进来
I'm sorry to drag you into this,
但检察官要求你为你父亲的案子
but the prosecutor is asking for you to give a deposition
出席取证会
regarding your father's case.
有什么能帮忙的吗
Anything I can do to help?
法庭的事  我还挺懂行的
I'm pretty courtroom savvy.
虽然我没看过每一集《法律与秩序》
I mean, I haven't seen every episode of Law & Order,
不过也看了大概400多集啦
just, like, 400 of them.
比如  法官的锤子不能叫"锤子"
For instance, the, uh, judge's hammer?
得叫惊堂木
Not called a hammer.
胃酸倒流  哎哟
Reflux! Oh!
抱歉
Sorry.
我吃片斯达舒就好了
I just... I need to take a Rylindia.
"斯达舒"啊  有效吗
Ah, Rylindia. Does that work?
大恩不言谢
You're welcome.
感谢你不远千里来找我
Well, thank you for coming all the way out here.
有你为我辩护  我很放心
I know I'm in good hands with you representing me.
卡洛琳  虽然我十分想帮你
Uh, well, Caroline, as much as I would love to help you
以及你的"律师"同伴
and your legal associate here,
但事务所不会同意让我免费帮你的
uh, the firm won't let me do it for free.
你老爸的案子差点把我们公司弄垮
I mean, your father's case bankrupted us practically,
而我的标准收费是一小时1100块
and my standard rate is $1,100 an hour.
我真的付不起这个钱
You know I don't have that kind of money.
上周我给自己除毛
Last week, I gave myself a bikini wax
还是用从餐厅偷的胶带呢
with duct tape I stole from the diner.
我得再吃颗斯达舒了
I'm gonna need another Rylindia.
注意  每小时只能服用一片
Oh, don't take two of those in under an hour
否则你就准备一打哈欠就高潮吧
unless you want to have an orgasm every time you yawn.
大恩不言谢哟
You're welcome again.
哈钦森先生  我真的很需要你的帮忙
Mr. Hutchinson, I need you to do this.
你能轻易搞定这件事情
You can make this go away as easily as possible.
别让我跪下求你了
Please don't make me beg.
这地板超脏  我裙子又太短
The floor's gross, and my skirt's too short.
律师  在这个关键时刻
Counselor, at this juncture,
我需要请钱宁小姐
I am going to need to take Miss Channing
到酒柜吧台处小议片刻
and have a sidebar over near the bar bar.
这真好玩啊  你说是吧
How fun is this, by the way?
我就跟你的代表律师似的
I'm, like, your lawyer now.
是好玩啊  就跟我上周除毛一样"好玩"
Oh, real fun. About as fun as that bikini wax.
害我得多花14块买止痛药
And then I had to spend $14 on neosporin.
别担心  我知道有一晚赚500的方法
Don't worry, I know how you can make $500 in one night.
她刚来店里我就问她要不要"赚"了
I've been telling her that since she got here.
麦克斯  我才不去当试药小白鼠
Max, I am not doing a drug trial.
而且  就算我去了钱也不够啊
Besides, it's not enough money anyway.
是不够  但可以把我的500给你
No, but after I put in my $500,
然后再从开店基金拿出100块
plus we take $100 from the cupcake fund.
我有想过有天可能会动用基金
You know, I always thought we'd have to use the cupcake money
来处理我们的法律问题
to get us out of a legal problem.
不过我一直以为是拿去救你
I just thought it'd be for you.
我也这么以为
Me too!
欢迎加入试药者联盟
Welcome aboard, drug buddy.
真没想到我会来做试药小白鼠
I can't believe I'm doing a drug trial.
我连甜菊代糖都不愿吃呢
I won't even use stevia.
这挺好玩的啦
It'll be fun!
就当是读书时期去朋友家过夜嘛
Just think of it as a middle-school sleepover.
但这得吃药
But with drugs.
读书时期不都是去嗑药过夜嘛
Yeah, a middle-school sleepover.
所以你以前做这个的时候
So when you did this before,
没出现过任何副作用对吧
you never got any side effects, right?
没有坏的副作用
Well, no negative ones.
想当年姐还是A罩杯呢
I used to be an "A" Cup.
大家看起来都好正常呢
Wow, everybody looks so normal.
和谐得像姐妹会而不是贫民窟
This is more like sorority row than skid row.
你好  我叫凯蒂
Hi! I'm Katie.
我才刚知道得三个人住一间
Just found out there's three to a room,
就来问问你们找到室友没
and I was wondering if you guys have chosen a roomie yet.
什么  三个人住一间啊
Wait, there's three in a room?
是啊
Yeah, I know.
所以选室友得慎重
You want to be careful who you get.
顺带一提  我有点自残倾向
Anyways, I'm a self-mutilator,
到时候你们能不能多照看我一点
and, um, I was wondering if you could keep an eye on me.
我一拿尖锐物就赶紧抢走
Just wrestle anything out of my hands that's sharp.
凯蒂  其实呢...
Uh, you know what, Katie?
我们也有自残倾向
We are self-mutilators too.
到时也会满手尖锐物  无暇照看你
So, uh, we kind of have our hands full.
对啊  我们到时候也会忙着
Yeah, we're gonna be super-busy
拼命地自残
self-mutilating ourselves.
那就不打扰了
No worries.
麦克斯  你怎么也不先告诉床位的事
Max, you should have told me about the bed situation.
当新药的小白鼠就算了
Untested experimental drugs is one thing,
可三人挤一间房  这还有人道吗
but three to a room? That's barbaric!
没事啦
It'll be fine!
选个好室友就行了
We just have to pick the right girl.
那个穿大衣的女孩如何
What about, uh, the one in the raincoat?
她看起来挺跩的
She looks stuck-up,
感觉会喋喋不休地谈论自己
like she'd talk about herself all night.
也对  我身旁就坐着一位这样的
Yeah, we already got one of those.
那...
What about, uh...
那个穿鲍勃·玛利衣服的妞如何
What about Bob Marley shirt?
感觉她会有体臭
She looks like she smells.
确认无误
Confirmed.
那边  就她了
Right there. That's who we want.
像个聪明人  又不会多管闲事
She looks smart and like she'd mind her own business.
你好啊  在干嘛呢
Hey! What are you up to?
没干嘛  在做自己的事而已
Nothing. Just minding my own business.
要跟我们一起住一间吗
Hey, want to be our roommate?
我刚答应了一个自残妹
Oh, I just said yes to a self-mutilator,
不过我也可以反悔啦
but I can get out of it.
爱自残的都喜欢被拒绝吧
She probably loves rejection.
女士们  听好啦
All right, ladies, listen up!
-嗨  麦克斯  -嗨  托比
- Hey, Max! - Hi, Toby.
先说好  我跟她  还有...
Heads-up, me, her, and, uh...
抱歉  你叫什么名字
Excuse me, what's your name?
无所谓的
Oh, it's cool,
不用问名字  装友善的
we don't have to do, like, the name thing.
深得我心的女孩啊
A girl after my own heart!
-我们住一间  -没问题
- We're roommates. - Got it.
在座大多数人都有经验了
Now, since most of you have done this before,
我就长话短说吧
I'll make it quick.
半数的人会吃到安慰剂
Half of you will get a placebo.
其他的将会吃到新药"角斗名伶"
The other half will be a testing a new drug called Gladiva,
别乱想  这是药名
and no, that's not my stage name
不是我在舞厅的"艺名"
down at the clubs.
好的  副作用会在
Okay, possible side effects
接下来24至48小时内出现
may occur over the next 24 to 48 hours.
可能出现的症状有...
They are... drum roll please...
头痛  呕吐  胃胀气
Headaches, vomiting, flatulence,
舌头肿大  自杀倾向
tongue-swelling, suicidal thoughts...
我现在就有这倾向了
I'm having some right now.
-行丧  -行走能力丧失
- I.T.W.... - Inability To Walk.
希望我会出现这个
Mm, I hope we get that
不然我死也不待这里
'cause that's the only thing that's gonna keep me here.
狂尿
And R.U....
狂尿不止
Relentless urination.
疲劳  抽搐
Fatigue, seizures...
骆驼趾
Camel toe.
开玩笑的  我开个玩笑而已
I'm kidding. That's my joke.
他就爱开这玩笑
That's his joke.
幸好  不然老娘早闪人了
Good, 'cause I was out the door.
还有例如TG  EB  CCS
Also, TG, EB, CCS...
要我解释给你听吗
You want me to explain those to you?
等我有了再解释吧
Not until you see one happening to me.
还有大失
And A.L.
大便失禁
Anal leakage.
副作用界的一姐哦
The Grande Dame of side effects.
吞干净吧
Well, bottoms up.
麦克斯  刚说完大便失禁谁还敢吞啊
Max, don't say that after "anal leakage."
还是不错的嘛
See? This is fun!
付钱让我们来吃饼干  玩桌游"人生之旅"
Getting paid to eat cookies and play the game of life.
-到你了  -有啥好玩的
- Your turn. - What's the point?
我的人生早就输得一败涂地了
Clearly, I've already lost the game of life
瞧我现在  当试药的小白鼠
'cause I'm sitting in a drug trial
等着我的"大失"呢
waiting for my "A" to "L".
如果你真中了"大失"
Well, if your "A" does start to "L",
就给我睡下边的床去
you're on the bottom bunk.
我要尿尿
I gotta pee.
惨喽
Ruh-roh.
怎么了
What?
应该没事啦
Mm, it's probably nothing,
不过也可能是"狂尿"
but she might be experiencing R.U.
那是什么意思来着
What's that again?
狂尿不止
Relentless urination.
人家就只是去尿个尿
She just said she had to pee.
这不就是狂尿吗
Yeah, that's relentless.
-你没事吧  -没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
你确"尿"吗
"R.U." sure?
好啦  到你转转盘了
Okay, your turn to spin.
不玩了
No more games.
我得好好准备取证会
I really want to be prepared for this deposition.
能读下哈钦森先生给我的问题吗
Can you read me the questions Mr. Hutchinson sent?
"请陈述全名"
"State your full name."
卡洛琳·维斯卜·钱宁
Caroline Wesbox Channing.
你的中间名叫"维斯卜"啊
Your middle name is "Wesbox"?
是从我祖父的名字来的
It was my grandfather's name.
听起来还像是副作用的名字呢
It also might be a side effect.
"我刚睡了个男人  结果染上猥湿步了"
"I just slept with a dude who gave me Wesbox!"
麦克斯  能赶紧问下个问题吗
Max, can you just ask me the next question?
你对于钱宁投资财团把手中的
Do you have any knowledge of investor capital
投资人资金转到外国账户
from the Channing investment group
有任何的了解吗
being transferred to offshore banks?
我完全不知情
I had no knowledge of it.
-你好无趣啊  -我无趣吗
- You're boring. - I'm boring?
如果这是电视剧  我早转台了
I'm just saying, I'd change the channel.
一点看头都没有
This is a bad one.
麦克斯  又不是《法律与秩序》
Max, it's not Law & Order.
我们哪比得上啊
I'll say it isn't.
明天  你得主动出击
Look, tomorrow, you gotta give them something.
领口拉低  裙子弄短
Open your shirt, hike up your skirt,
给他们看你的"微湿部"
show them your Wesbox.
"你对于你父亲非法吸金一事
"Did you know anything about your father
-有任何了解吗"  -不知道
- "illegally siphoning funds?" - No.
"你父亲跟你谈有关转钱
"Have you ever had any conversations
或相关事宜的事情吗"
with your father regarding said transactions?"
没有
No.
"你现在是处于大便失禁状态吗"
"Is your ass leaking right now?"
没有
No.
惨喽
Ruh-roh.
还没完
Nope.
你们一切安好吗
How we doing, ladies?
有出现副作用吗
Any side effects?
麦克斯  你睡着了吗
Max, are you awake?
麦克斯
Max!
安静  不然你要吵到嘘嘘·死被洗裤了
Quiet, you're gonna wake up Pissy Spacek.
我睡不着  我的心砰砰跳个不停
I can't sleep. My hearts keeps racing.
你得通知托比  应该是出现了副作用
You should tell Toby. It's probably a side effect.
不是  我是紧张
No, I'm nervous.
脑海中一直想着这场取证会和我老爸
I can't stop thinking about the deposition and about my father.
我能下来跟你聊聊吗
Can I come down and talk?
不太方便啊  我这儿有人呢
Not a great time. I kind of have people over.
进来吧  怎么啦
Get in here. What's wrong?
我好担心明天的事
I'm scared about tomorrow.
我好怕我说错话
I'm scared I'm gonna say the wrong thing
害我老爸得多受牢狱之灾
and make things worse for my father.
人家问一句你答一句
Look, all you have to do is answer the questions
别自由发挥就行了
as carefully as they suggested
然后抛个媚眼  别穿内裤去
and then throw in a wink, forget to wear panties.
你爹就没事了
He'll be fine.
重点就在这
But that's the thing.
这些问题根本问不出我父亲的为人
The questions don't say anything about my father.
都是些公式化的问题
They're so cut and dry.
他们问的细枝末节  我一无所知
They're only asking me details about things I know nothing about,
而我所知的一切  他们又一概不问
and they're not interested in the things I do know about him.
无视他是一个温柔风趣  慷慨慈爱的父亲
That he's warm, and funny, and generous, and loving.
还记得我小时候
Like when I was little,
我们搭私人飞机  去我们的滑雪度假屋时...
and he and I would take our plane to our chalet in Deer Valley.
停  你这么说  就跟说
Stop. You might as well rephrase that to
"他跟我搭着罪孽来到
"When he and I would take our guilty
罪孽的罪孽小屋"一样
to our guilty in guilty valley."
每天早晨  我们去滑雪前
Every morning, before we went skiing,
他都会起个大早  给我做
he would get up really early and make me
他招牌的雪花肉桂法式吐司
his snowflake cinnamon french toast.
感觉挺棒的
Sounds amazing.
他会把肉桂跟糖慢慢地撒在吐司上
And as he dusted the cinnamon and sugar on top,
然后说"小宝贝  快看  在下雪呢
he'd say, "look, sweetheart, it's snowing,
只属于你的雪哦"
snowing just for you."
然后他会把吐司切成小...
And then he'd cut it into these little pieces...
你看  我都语塞说不出口了
See? I can't even get the words out.
没人想听  也没人会知道他有多好
No one will ever hear them. No one will know.
我知道啊  我听了
I'll know. I heard them.
又去吗
Another round?
是啊  我直接带枕头进去吧
Yeah, I'm just gonna bring my pillow in there.
估计这"角斗女伶"是没希望推出市场了
I don't think Gladiva's gonna make it to the market.
取证会将会在这里举行
We'll be doing the deposition in here.
哇  跟《法律与秩序》里看起来一摸一样呢
Oh, wow, this is exactly how it looks on Law & Order!
还有台迷你打字机
There's the tiny typewriter thing
那个无台词的女龙套就坐在这里
where the actress who never gets to speak sits!
里欧  能帮我跟打字机合个影吗
Leo, Leo, take my picture near the tiny typewriter.
女士们  我们只有一小时的时间
Ladies, ladies. We only have an hour.
由于你们迟到  进度已经落后了
We're already behind because you were late.
抱歉  我们刚去兑现支票
Sorry, we had to stop at the check-cashing place.
然后去店里帮一个朋友买尿布
Yeah, and then a store to get diapers for a friend.
给  1000块
There, $1,000.
顺顺利利  "无屎无病"
No fuss, and luckily, no muss.
麦克斯  开店基金的100块带了吗
Max, do you have the $100 from the cupcakes?
带了
Yeah.
40  60  80  90
Uh, 40... 60... 80... 90...
5  6  7  还有...
5, 6, 7, and...
100  齐啦
100.
哈钦森先生  你又胃酸倒流了吗
Mr. Hutchinson, are you having reflux?
没  只是突然对我的工作感慨万千
No, I-it just became clear to me what I do for a living.
卡洛琳
Okay, uh, Caroline,
你准备好了  我就去带人进来
if you're ready, I can bring them in.
记住  问一句答一句
Remember, just stick to the questions
千万别自由发挥
and don't embellish.
里欧  我昨晚教过她了
I prepped her last night, Leo.
好了  麦克斯  你该走了
All right, let's go, Max.
我想她留下来
Actually, I want her to stay.
我好紧张  她在场我比较放松
I'm nervous, and she makes me feel better.
我是她的已注册情感伴侣
Yes, I'm her registered emotional companion.
这是正经的法律程序
Well, this is a legal proceeding,
这样的要求是很不寻常的
and that's a highly unusual request.
也不是不允许啊  我们上网查过了
But not improbable. We googled it.
她有权带着情绪伴侣出席取证会
Yeah, she's allowed to have an emotional companion,
只要双方律师同意就行
as long as both attorneys agree.
虽然我这哈佛毕业的尖子生都没听过
Well, I graduated top of my class at Harvard,
不过既然你们都上网搜过了  那我试试吧
but since you googled it, I'll try to make that happen.
我对于你所提的转账  毫不知情
No, I am unaware of any of the transactions you just mentioned.
谢谢  钱宁小姐
Thank you, Miss Channing.
麻烦你再稍等片刻
Now, if you'll just bear with me a little while longer,
我还剩几道问题就问完了
I only have a couple more pertinent questions.
你的声音也太酷了吧
Your voice is unbelievable.
绝对有《秩序与法律》的范儿
You could be on Law & Order.
麦克斯
Max!
撤回
Withdrawn.
钱宁小姐  你对于钱宁投资财团的
Miss Channing, do you have any knowledge of embezzlement
一切诈财事宜有任何了解吗
of any kind taking place at the Channing investment group?
不知道  我完...
No, I had no knowl...
全...
of any su...
你能再说一次吗
Could you repeat that?
惨喽
Ruh-roh.
你出现副作用了
You're having a side effect!
舌肿  舌头肿大
Tongue swelling. TS!
律师  给我们一点时间
Uh, counselor, give us one second.
怎么回事
What is going on?
我们吃了药[毒品]
We took drugs.
你刚是说你们磕了药吗
Did she just say "we took drugs"?
厉害啊  里欧  你不玩你比我猜可惜了
Very good, Leo. You must play charades.
为了付你的律师费  我们去参加药物试验
Look, we did a drug trial to get money for this.
律师 在等什么呢
What's the holdup, counselor?
让她喝点水  我也试过这样
Just give her some water. I had this once.
一个小时后就没事了
It goes away in an hour.
你不是说你没出现过任何副作用吗
You said you never had any side effects!
拜托  我都去鬼门关走过一回了
Oh, please. I died once.
我只是不想吓着你
I just didn't want to scare you.
钱宁小姐  你知道你父亲有任何
Miss Channing, are you aware of any accounts
未注册在他名下的资产吗
opened under any names other than your father's?
喝点水吧
Just drink the water.
等一下
One sec.
有人有纸巾或围兜吗
Uh, does anyone have a napkin or a bib?
1100大洋呢  这里不会连围兜都没有吧
$1,100, you gotta have a bib around here somewhere.
这到底是怎么一回事
All right, what's going on here?
我刚刚得知我的委托人
I was just, uh, informed my client
再过去的24小时里  参加了药物试验
was part of a drug test within the last 24 hours.
药物试验  里欧
Drug test, Leo?
这借口不错啊
That's a good one.
不就是另一个吸毒的富家女嘛
Just another rich girl on drugs.
送去勒戒所  取证会重新安排时间吧
Get her into rehab, and we'll have to reschedule.
我们下次再继续吧
We'll have to do this another time.
不行  不行  不行
No, no, no, no, no, no!
不行  她说得对
No, no! She's right!
我们付不起钱再折腾一次了
We don't have the money to do this another time
我来告诉你们吧
look, I can tell you right now,
她什么都不知道
she does not know anything.
不知道钱哪来的
She doesn't know about the money,
不知道任何转账
she doesn't know about transactions.
她对一切都一无所知
She doesn't know anything about anything.
而我们付的钱还有三分钟才结束
We are paid up for three more minutes,
我们就要物尽其用
and we are going to use them!
虽然她无法说  但我知道她想说什么
She can't talk, but I know what she would want to say.
房间里的  先生们女士们
Ladies and gentlemen of the... room,
她想告诉你们她爸爸真实的样子
she would want you to know who her father really is.
他以前会为她做雪吐司
He used to make her snow toast!
她说过  他是一个风趣  聪明
And in her words, he was funny, smart,
慷慨的爱人
and a generous lover.
是慷慨和慈爱
Generous and loving!
抱歉  是的  是慷慨和慈爱
Oh, sorry, yes, yes. Generous and loving.
虽然我不认识她老爸  也没见过他
Now, I don't know her father, and I have never met him...
不过请把我说的写入记录
And I would like you to put that on the record,
麻烦你了  没台词的龙套小姐
actress who's never allowed to talk...
可是我跟她很熟  而她是个很棒的人
But I do know her, and she's an amazing person.
他爸爸独自抚养她成人
And her father raised her alone,
想必他也是个很棒的人
so he must be an amazing person too.
基本上
Well...
刚那些话屁都不算
That accomplished nothing.
律师  你说该怎么办呢
Counselor, what do we do here?
我们稍作休息  直到她能重新说话后
We take a short recess until she can speak,
再继续取证会  费用我包
and resume the deposition, on me,
因为他爸爸是个很棒的人  而且
because her father is an amazing guy, and...
《法律与秩序》里的人也会这么做的
that's what they would do on Law & Order.
好吧  我们休息一小时
Fine, we'll break for an hour.
说真的  你的声音像超级英雄的老板
Seriously, you sound like a superhero's boss.
麦克斯  你真厉害
Max, you're the best.
的确  我是挺厉害的呀
I know. I did pretty good, right?
早知道我就去读法学院了
I should've gone to law school.
或读个高中
Or High School.
请求进入法官内庭
Permission to enter the judge's chambers?
请求通过
Permission granted.
别介意这些蓝起司
Excuse the tubs of blue cheese.
它们是我没有在这偷吃东西的证据
They're being held as evidence in the case against eating here.
我想感谢你为我做的一切
I wanted to thank you for everything you did.
我知道你本来是打算拿试药的钱
And I know you were gonna buy yourself a treat
给自己买点小礼物
with the drug money...
是啊  买药嗑
Yeah, like drugs.
所以我买了份小礼物送你
So I got you a little something.
《法律与秩序》大全集
It's the complete Law & Order box set!
不是吧
No way!
这哪是小礼物  这要500大洋呢
That's not a little something. That's, like, $500.
地铁那只卖30块
Or $30 on the subway.
卖的人说  大部分都是英语版的哦
And the guy said most of them are in english.
帅呆了
Awesome!
冷冻库休庭
Freezer adjourned.